<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StreamTV</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="movie_name">Movie</string>
    <string name="about_us1">About Us</string>
    <string name="infoby"> Information by: TMDB API </string>
    <string name="madeBy"> Made by: Disha Poojary </string>
    <string name="about_us"> StreamTV is a app made for providing movies, tv shows for people to enjoy as a source of entertainment.\nAll the movies, tv shows, documentary,etc. are from a legitimate site and is made available to this app using a renowned API called TMDB i.e. <b>The Movie DataBase.</b> \nThe nearly millions of entertaiment shows and movies available will surely make your experience amazing.\nUsers can find, save and share their favourite shows. \nWith a deep understanding of user preferences, we offer powerful, data-driven tools to build lasting customer relationships and drive sales and revenue at scale. TMDB officially supports 39 languages, also have extensive regional data. Every single day TMDB is used in over 180 countries.
    </string>
    <string name="term_con">These user terms are referred to in them as:\nYour access to and use of our services through Your Account with us, all functionality on our Site, applications, buttons, browser plugins, application programming interfaces, and accessing functionality on third parties who have integrated them into their experiences.\nThe rules that apply to any recipes or other information, text, graphics, photos or other materials or content available on the StreamTV.\n\n<b>Duties and Rights of Users</b>\nThe data required for registration must be provided truthfully to ensure smooth use.\nYou are responsible for protecting your registration and access data (e.g., user name, password) and you should not disclose them or tolerate or enable unauthorized or third parties to find them out. You are obliged to take the required measures to guarantee confidentiality.\nAs part of the community functions you have the option to set up your own content in your profile (e.g., personal information, profile picture) and the database of StreamTV content (e.g., movies).\nThe user may not decompile the App or otherwise reverse engineer it or try to find out the source code. An exception to this are actions that are necessary to obtain interface information required to ensure interoperability of the App with third-party software; this requires that the user has previously made unsuccessful attempts to find out such information.\nChanges to the Terms of Use StreamTV may change and adapt these Terms of Use for the use of community functions effective for the future, if this is necessitated by changes in the legal and economic general conditions. StreamTV will send the amended Terms of Use to the user at least six weeks before the planned entry into effect per e-mail and point out especially the new provision. At the same time, StreamTV will set a reasonable period of at least six weeks for the user to declare the acceptance of the amended Terms of Use for the further use of services. If no declaration of acceptance is made within this period, since the receipt of the information, the amended Terms of Use will be considered accepted.\n\n\n\n<b>Updated in:</b> March 2023
    </string>
    <string name="terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="plot">This section will provide a brief overview about the film or tv show, i.e its plot.</string>
</resources>